https://www.camline.com/privacy-policy/

ProductsProductsLineWorksCornerstoneXperiDeskInFrame Synapse
MenuLineWorksCornerstoneXperiDeskInFrame SynapseMES modules for large-scale production and mass production. Enables the digital transformation of your high-tech manufacturing process.Desktop software for data analysis, developed with engineers in mind. Enhance your team’s ability to carry out technical data analysis.The innovative software for R&D departments, forming the backbone of your knowledge management to help you bring products to market faster.Powerful Manufacturing Execution System (MES) for manufacturers of discrete
medical products and medical
devices.ExpertiseExpertiseOur expertise makes the differenceBenefit from the passion and decades of experience that camLine puts into the development of its in-house software solutions every single day. Our expertise enables faster data access, increases process security, and shortens response times and downtimes. Our products are divided into four different brands that support you in all areas, from innovation to production.IndustriesIndustriesSemiconductorsOne of the world’s top software solution providers for the semiconductor industry for over 30 years.ElectronicsOptimise your electronics manufacturing with our MES software.AutomotiveMove your production into the fast lane.Medical equipmentTop manufacturing solutions for a clean bill of health.Materials scienceVital system landscape for agile teams, designed for high data throughput.SolarSunny times: We offer a coordinated solution in the form of MES Solar.R&DGreater efficiency in the development of manufacturing technologies.CareerCareerJobs @ camLineThe world of production is changing rapidly. The question is: What do we contribute to Industry 4.0? The answer is simple: At camLine, we are developing the manufacturing software solutions of tomorrow already today. Be a part of it.ContactContact/ Support camLine Holding AG camLine GmbHIndustriering 4a85238 PetershausenGermanyPhone: + 49 (0) 8137 935-0E-Mail:
info(@)camLine.comYou needSupport? If you do not have access to your support account, please call camLine atPhone: + 49 (0) 8137 935 0or write to administration(@)camline.com
Support Login Support Login academyacademyCoursesVision & Mission
MenuCoursesVision & MissionDiscover our wide range of courses.Our team provides you with unique expert knowledge and know-how.
MenuProductsLineWorksCornerstoneXperiDeskInFrame SynapseExpertiseIndustriesCareerContactSupportacademyCoursesVision & Mission
Search
CloseDEEN Privacy PolicyInformation on Data Protection for CustomersController of the data processing:camLine Holding AGIndustriering 4a85238 PetershausenGermanyLegal representatives:Heinz Linsmaier (CEO)Bernhard Jofer (VP)Chee Cheong Ng (Bryan Ng, VP)Hong Sin Goh (Mitch Goh, VP)Controller’s Data Protection Officer:Data Protection Officer camLineIndustriering 4a85238 Petershausen, Germanyprivacy@camline.comMore detailed information on data processing is available via the following link: Customer Information Sheet PreambleThe following contains information about how we process personal data in connection with the use of our website. Personal data is all data pertaining to you personally, e.g. name, address, email address, usage behavior.General data collection during retrieval of our websiteIf you only use this website for information purposes, we will only collect the personal data relayed by your browser to our server. If you wish to view our website, we will collect the following data, which we need for technical reasons in order to display our website to you, and to ensure its stability and security (the legal basis for this is legitimate interest according to Art. 6 (1) 1 f GDPR).As part of balancing interests performed in accordance with Art. 6 (1) f GDPR, we have considered and weighed up our interest in the provision of your personal data alongside your interest in processing of your personal data that complies with data protection. Because the following data may sometimes be necessary for technical reasons in the delivery of our services, or to ensure stability and security, in particular protection against misuse, we have come to the conclusion that this data may be processed – using a guarantee of state-of-the-art data security and taking due account of your interest in data protection-compliant processing.As part of balancing interests performed in accordance with Art. 6 (1) f GDPR, we have considered and weighed up our interest in the provision of your personal data alongside your interest in processing of your personal data that complies with data protection. Because the following data may sometimes be necessary for technical reasons in the delivery of our services, or to ensure stability and security, in particular protection against misuse, we have come to the conclusion that this data may be processed – using a guarantee of state-of-the-art data security and taking due account of your interest in data protection-compliant processing.
Operating system usedAnalysis of devices to ensure optimized website display (“responsive design”)
Information concerning the browser type and the version usedAnalysis of the browser used, in order to optimize our website for this purpose
IP addressDisplaying our website on the applicable device
Date and time of accessEnsuring proper operation of the website, especially the response times of our system
Where relevant, the manufacturer and type designation of your smartphone, tablet or other terminal devicesAnalysis of the device manufacturer and types of mobile terminal devices for statistical purposes
Log filesEnsuring that the website operates properlyStorage periodThe data will be erased when you end your session. System maintenance will store the data in log files for 7 days in order to monitor and improve the stability of the system.Recording data and the storage of this data in log files are essential for the availability and operation of the website. The user therefore has no right to object in this regard.CookiesCookies – General InformationOur website uses cookies. Cookies are text files stored on the internet browser itself or by the internet browser on the user’s computer system. A cookie may be stored on the user’s operating system when the user accesses an online site. This cookie contains a distinctive character string, which allows the browser to be clearly identified the next time that the website is viewed.Cookies – different types of cookies(a) Cookies necessary for technical reasonsWe use cookies to make our website more user-friendly. Certain elements of our website require the ability to identify the accessing browser even following a page change.Name of the Cookie: CM-System WordPress
Purpose of the processing: Data and information management in the backend of the homepage (editorial management of the homepage)
Legal basis of the processing: legitimate interest
Storage period: only for duration of current sessionCookies that are necessary for technical reasons are not strictly needed in order to display the website. However, some of the functions of the website cannot be properly used without these cookies. The user therefore has no right to object in this regard; these cookies can be blocked using the setting of the relevant browser.(b) Cookies for measurement of reachCookies for collecting range information about the use of our website, e.g. website views or error messages. These cookies do not store any information enabling the user to be identified. The collected information will only ever be aggregated and analyzed anonymously.EssentialEssential cookies enable basic functions and are necessary for the proper function of the website.Borlabs CookieNameBorlabs CookieProviderOwner of this websitePurposeSaves the visitors preferences selected in the Cookie Box of Borlabs Cookie.Cookie Nameborlabs-cookieCookie Expiry1 YearWPMLNameWPMLProviderOwner of this websitePurposeSaves current language of the websiteCookie Namewp-wpml_current_languageCookie Expiry1 DayGoogle reCaptchaNameGoogle reCaptchaProviderGooglePurposeBlocks Bots and Spam requests on forms.Purposehttps://www.google.com/intl/de/policies/privacy/Host(s).google.comCookie NameNIDCookie Expiry1 YearStatisticsStatistics cookies collect information anonymously. This information helps us to understand how our visitors use our website.MarketingMarketing cookies are used by third-party advertisers or publishers to display personalized ads. They do this by tracking visitors across websites.External MediaContent from video platforms and social media platforms is blocked by default. If External Media cookies are accepted, access to those contents no longer requires manual consent.YouTubeNameYouTubeProviderYouTubePurposeUsed to unblock YouTube content.Purposehttps://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en&gl=enHost(s)google.comCookie NameNIDCookie Expiry6 MonthYouTubeOur website contains links to videos provided by YouTube, which is operated by Google. The system operator is Google Ireland Limited, Gordon House, Barrow Street, Dublin 4, Ireland. A connection to YouTube’s servers will be established only when you actively click on a linked video. As long as you do not leave our website, no data exchange with YouTube can take place. We have marked the relevant points with the appropriate information.NewsletterNewsletter (eLetter)If you subscribe to our newsletter, camLine will send you current information about our Service Offering Portfolio (SOP). If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter, you can, at any time, object to the use of your email address for this purpose. You can indicate the withdrawal of your consent by using the link provided in every newsletter email, or by sending an email to unsubscribe(at)camLine.com.We use the double opt-in procedure for subscriptions to our newsletter. This means that following your email registration, we will send an e-mail to your specified e-mail address to confirm your request to receive the newsletter. If you do not confirm this within 24 hours, your registration will be deleted automatically.
Name of the newsletter provider Inxmail GmbH Wentzingerstr. 17 79106 Freiburg, GermanyType of service provider: ProcessorData transmission to third country: NOSafeguards in accordance with Art. 44 et seqq. GDPR: NO
Data: Time of log-inPurpose of the processing: Proof of the double opt-inLegal basis of the processing: ConsentStorage period: 3 years to the end of the year following the erasure of the data for delivery of the newsletter
Data: IP address for DOIPurpose of the processing: Proof of the double opt-inLegal basis of the processing: ConsentStorage period: 3 years to the end of the year following the erasure of the data for delivery of the newsletter
Data: Time of the DOI verificationPurpose of the processing: Proof of the double opt-inLegal basis of the processing: ConsentStorage period: 3 years to the end of the year following the erasure of the data for delivery of the newsletter
Data: *Email addressPurpose of the processing: Sending the newsletterLegal basis of the processing: ConsentStorage period: until withdrawal of consent/objection
Data: TitlePurpose of the processing: Directly communicating with recipientLegal basis of the processing: ConsentDuration of storage: until withdrawal of consent/objection
Data: First namePurpose of the processing: Directly communicating with recipientLegal basis of the processing: ConsentDuration of storage: until withdrawal of consent/objection
Data: SurnamePurpose of the processing: Directly communicating with recipientLegal basis of the processing: ConsentDuration of storage: until withdrawal of consent/objection* Required fieldAnalysis of the NewsletterPlease note that we analyze your usage behavior in connection with receiving the newsletter (“count tracking”). To enable this evaluation, the e-mails sent include “web beacons” or tracking pixels. These are single-pixel image files that link to our website and enable us to analyze your usage behavior. This is then carried out by collecting web beacons, which are linked with a dedicated ID. The links in the newsletter also contain these. The data will be recorded in an anonymized form, so that the IDs are not linked with your other personal data, meaning that any direct personal reference to you is prevented. The information collected in this way is stored by the newsletter provider on its servers in Germany.Contact & ApplicationsContact formYou can contact us using our email address or the contact form. Personal data transmitted in this way will, of course, only be used for the purpose for which you provided it when contacting us. You can contact us using our email address or the contact form. Personal data transmitted in this way will, of course, only be used for the purpose for which you provided it when contacting us.
Description and extent of the data processingWe can be contacted via our contact form or via the email address indicated. The personal data of the sender (the user) transferred with the request are in turn stored.
Legal basis for the data processingThe legal basis for the processing of the data transferred concomitantly with the sending of a request is Art. 6 section 1 (f) GDPR (our legitimate interest as controller). Should the request be for the purpose of concluding an agreement, an additional legal basis for the processing is Art. 6 section 1 (b) GDPR (fulfilment of an agreement).
Purpose of the data processingThe processing of the personal data is used by us solely for the purpose of establishing contact.
Duration of retention Purpose of the processing: Proof of the double opt-in Legal basis of the processing: Consent Storage period: 3 years to the end of the year following the erasure of the data for delivering the newsletter
Option to lodge objectionThe user at all times has the option to lodge objection to the processing of their personal data. Objection can be lodged via the following email address: privacy(at)camLine.com. All personal data stored concomitantly with establishing contact will then be deleted.ApplicationsYou can submit your application to our company electronically. We will, of course, only use your information for processing your application and it will not be passed on to third parties. Please note that application data is transmitted unencrypted.We manage the application process on a centralized basis. Please note that by submitting an application, you are submitting an application to the camLine Group of companies; this will enable us to process your application data as quickly as possible. Detailed information on data processing in connection with the application process is available from the following link: Information Sheet for Applicants.Transmission of dataYour personal data will not be communicated to any third parties for any purposes other than those described here.We will only pass your personal data on to third parties if:
You have given your explicit consent for us to do so.
The transfer is necessary for the purposes of legitimate interests and there is no reason to assume that you have an overriding interest worthy of protection in not transferring your data.
The transfer is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation.
It is lawful and necessary for the performance of a contract with you.Data transmissions performed outside of the European Union do not generally take place with the high level of protection that exists within Europe. In the case of such a transmission, it may be there is currently no EU Commission adequacy decision within the definition of Art. 45 (1), 3 GDPR. That means that, to date, the Commission has not decided that the level of protection specific to each country corresponds to the level of data protection based on the GDPR, which is why we have created the appropriate safeguards set out above.Possible risks that might not be completely precluded in connection with the transmission of data particularly include:
Your personal data may possibly be processed over and beyond the actual purpose.
There is the possibility that you will not always be able to establish and implement your data protection rights, including, for example, your right to access, correction, erasure and data portability.
There is possibly also a greater likelihood that data processing will not be properly carried out, and that protection provided for the personal data does not quantitatively and qualitatively correspond to the requirements of the GDPR.InformationInformation concerning the rights of data subjects (valid from 25 May 2018)Every data subject has the right of access according to Art. 15 GDPR, the right to rectification according to Art. 16 GDPR, the right to erasure according to Art. 17 GDPR, the right to restriction of processing according to Art. 18 GDPR, the right to objection according to Art. 21 GDPR, as well as the right to data portability established in Art. 20 GDPR. The restrictions set out in Sections 34 and 35 Federal Data Protection Act [Bundesdatenschutzgesetz, BDSG] apply to the right to access (confirmation) and the right to erasure.Information concerning your right to file a complaintYou also have the right to file a complaint with the competent data protection supervisory authority about our processing of your personal data.Information concerning the withdrawal of consentYou may withdraw your consent to our processing your personal data at any time. This also applies to revoking consent issued to us before the General Data Protection Regulation came into effect, i.e. before 25 May 2018. Please note that the withdrawal will not affect data processing that has already been carried out. This will not affect any processing carried out prior to the withdrawal of consent.Rights in connection with data processing performed for the purpose of direct marketingIn accordance with Art. 21 (2) GDPR, you have the right to object at any time to the processing of personal data about you. If you object to processing for direct marketing purposes, we will no longer process the personal data for such purposes. Please note that the objection will only apply with future effect. This will not affect any processing carried out prior to the objection.Information concerning your right to object in connection with a balance of interestsIf we base the processing of your personal data on a balance of interests, you may object to the processing. If you choose to exercise your right to object, we request you to provide us with the reasons why your personal data should not be processed in the manner carried out by us. If your objection is justified, we will examine the matter and either cease or modify the data processing, or explain the compelling, legitimate grounds which form the basis of our continued processing.Links to other websitesOur web pages may contain links to other providers. Please note that this Privacy Statement applies to the website of camLine Holding AG only. We have no influence or control over whether other provides comply with the applicable data protection provisions.Amendments to the Privacy StatementWe reserve the right to amend or adapt this Privacy Statement at any time, in accordance with the applicable data protection provisions.Empfehlungsbund JobwidgetWe use the Empfehlungsbund Jobwidget provided bei pludoni GmbH (https://www.pludoni.de/impressum) to display job ads from our company on certain areas of our website (career website). When visiting our career website, a one-time secure connection is established via HTTPS to https://bms.empfehlungsbund.de. This connection is required to display our job advertisements. Log files are created which contain access data (name of the website accessed, file, date and time of access, amount of data transferred, notification of successful access, browser type and version, the user’s operating system, referrer URL (the previously visited site), IP address and the requesting provider). Log files are processed for the purpose of troubleshooting and for security reasons (e.g. to clarify misuse or fraud) and are stored for a maximum period of 3 months and then deleted. Data whose further storage is required for evidential purposes is excluded from deletion until final clarification of the respective incident. The legal basis according to the DSGVO is Art. 6, para. 1b, or Art. 28 (processor). As contractor, pludoni GmbH processes all data on our behalf. For detailed information on the processing of your data associated with the Empfehlungsbund Jobwidget, please refer to the separate data protection declaration (https://bms.empfehlungsbund.de/datenschutz#stellenanzeigen-widget) of pludoni GmbH.
Company
First name, last name*
Email*
Your message*
I accept the privacy policy* The fields marked with an asterisk (*) are mandatory.You can use this contact form to contact us. We will use your personal data only for the purpose of processing your query. Your contact request will be processed centrally within the camLine Group to ensure that your inquiry can be responded to as quickly and effectively as possible. More detailed information concerning the collection and processing of data in connection with this contact form is available in our Privacy Policy.
